module.exports = [{"category":"inventions","question":"Where would you be most likely to find Professor P's phone?","answers":["In Sleepy's basket","On the hall table","In the living room"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the best way to find Professor P's phone?","answers":["Call out and ask it where it is","Ask Sleepy to go and fetch it","Wait for it to ring"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions is polite and helpful?","answers":["His phone","His fridge","His dishwasher"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Professor P's fridge is","answers":["Grumpy","Helpful","Funny"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the best way to open Professor P's fridge?","answers":["Ask it nicely","Yank the handle hard","Prise it open with a screwdriver"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions is bad tempered?","answers":["His fridge","His toaster","His washing machine"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Professor P's toaster","answers":["Tells jokes","Explodes!","Hates mornings"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Professor P's toaster","answers":["Sometimes burns toast","Never burns toast","Always burns toast"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions tells jokes?","answers":["His toaster","His fridge","His dishwasher"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions doesn't know when to stop talking?","answers":["His toaster","His phone","His washing machine"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Professor P's front door","answers":["Talks in a loud commanding voice","Often bursts into fits of giggles","Laughs loudly"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions talks in a loud commanding voice?","answers":["His front door","His phone","His watch"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What's unusual about Professor P's cans of self-heating beans?","answers":["They sometimes explode","They always explode","They don't heat up the beans"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions is most likely to explode","answers":["His can of self-heating beans","His toaster","His phone"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about Professor P dishwasher","answers":["Nothing, it's just an ordinary dishwasher","It also washes clothes","It often breaks the dishes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's inventions does not talk?","answers":["His dishwasher","His phone","His watch"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What colour is Professor P's watch?","answers":["Purple","Pink","Blue"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about Professor P's watch?","answers":["It reminds him of appointments","It often gets the time wrong","It keeps falling off his wrist"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the problem with Professor P's automatic dog bathing machine?","answers":["It pulled some hairs out of Sleepy","It doesn't get Sleepy clean","Nothing, it works fine."]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the problem with Professor P's electric flea comb?","answers":["It gave Sleepy an electric shock","It doesn't kill fleas","Nothing, it works fine"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the problem with Professor P's automatic pet feeder?","answers":["Nothing, it works fine","It gave Professor P's cats an electric shock","It explodes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"Which of Professor P's pet products works very well?","answers":["The automatic pet feeder","The automatic dog bathing machine","The electric flea comb"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What's special about Professor P's solar powered kettle?","answers":["It can use sea water","It tells jokes","It explodes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What's special about Professor P's dinghy?","answers":["It's solar powered and self-inflating","Nothing, it's just an ordinary dinghy","It explodes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"The metal detector Peter and Tara built","answers":["Blew up","Worked fine","Did not have enough capacitors"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about the lights in Professor P's basement?","answers":["They won't switch on unless you say â€˜please'","They switch on automatically","They don't work"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is the problem with Professor P's solar powered cool box?","answers":["There's no room for the food","It freezes the food","It explodes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about the coloured balls in Professor P's basement?","answers":["They don't stop bouncing","They explode","Nothing, they are just ordinary plastic balls"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about the Professor P's answer phone?","answers":["It won't let you talk to Professor P if you're trying to sell something","It doesn't record messages","It explodes"]},{"category":"inventions","question":"What is unusual about the Professor P's answer phone?","answers":["It sings badly","Nothing, it works fine","It explodes"]}]